<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>beans on Beans, Bread, Books</title><link>https://beansbreadbooks.jonahweissman.com/tags/beans/</link><description>Recent content in beans on Beans, Bread, Books</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 16:29:15 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://beansbreadbooks.jonahweissman.com/tags/beans/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Here I Go Again</title><link>https://beansbreadbooks.jonahweissman.com/post/here-i-go-again/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 16:29:15 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://beansbreadbooks.jonahweissman.com/post/here-i-go-again/</guid><description>I am on the Capital Limited (train 29) to Chicago. Here is a list of things that make this trip different:
My trip begins in DC (this shaves a couple of hours and like $50 off of the trip) It is winter (previous trips have been in the summer). I will provide updates on if this changes my experience at all I have left my beans intact and added less brine.</description></item><item><title>Returning to Charlottesville</title><link>https://beansbreadbooks.jonahweissman.com/post/returning-to-charlottesville/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Sep 2022 16:55:40 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://beansbreadbooks.jonahweissman.com/post/returning-to-charlottesville/</guid><description>I am sitting on the California Zephyr, train 6 to Chicago. The familiar rumble of the tracks is gone, the train sits still. We await the cargo train ahead of us. Its crew is walking the length of the mile plus long train, looking for mechanical problems.
Part of my hesitancy to create a blog was a fear that I would be sucked into a world of gamified social interactions, that could mess with my incentives.</description></item><item><title>Beans Are Now Alcoholic</title><link>https://beansbreadbooks.jonahweissman.com/post/beans-are-now-alcoholic/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 16:37:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://beansbreadbooks.jonahweissman.com/post/beans-are-now-alcoholic/</guid><description>My bag of beans is now rapidly swelling with gas. When I open it, I&amp;rsquo;m hit with a wave of vapors that makes me recoil. It tastes like rubbing alcohol, even when mixed with ketchup.
Fortunately, I&amp;rsquo;ll arrive in only a few hours.</description></item><item><title>Responses to Reader Questions</title><link>https://beansbreadbooks.jonahweissman.com/post/responses-to-reader-questions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 08:53:09 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://beansbreadbooks.jonahweissman.com/post/responses-to-reader-questions/</guid><description>what books pair best with your beans
I started Ministry for the Future by Kim Stanley Robinson last night. It&amp;rsquo;s an explicitly longtermist sci fi book (although focused on a very short time horizon so far) about responses to climate change. It is the best pairing with my beans so far because my beans inspire the same sense of fear for the future and need for perseverance, modulated by human intervention (ketchup and garlic), as the book.</description></item><item><title>Vegan Blue Corn Tamale</title><link>https://beansbreadbooks.jonahweissman.com/post/vegan-blue-corn-tamale/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 00:48:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://beansbreadbooks.jonahweissman.com/post/vegan-blue-corn-tamale/</guid><description>I got a vegan blue corn tamale from the dining car. Mushy and uninspired, $5. But worth every penny because while I was there I pilfered 5 packets of ketchup, mustard and relish, which have increased the palatability of my beans dramatically. Much needed.</description></item><item><title>first snack</title><link>https://beansbreadbooks.jonahweissman.com/post/2022-08-26T1620-0400/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://beansbreadbooks.jonahweissman.com/post/2022-08-26T1620-0400/</guid><description>Several updates: we passed Afton mountain and entered the Shenandoah valley. We passed the other Cardinal train, heading in the opposite direction. And I tried my beans and bread! The beans are very salty, but the flavor is complex enough to keep me entertained. The bread (baked last night) is delicious.</description></item><item><title>Leaving Charlottesville</title><link>https://beansbreadbooks.jonahweissman.com/post/2022-08-26T1337-0400/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://beansbreadbooks.jonahweissman.com/post/2022-08-26T1337-0400/</guid><description>My train to Chicago (number 51) is running an hour and a half late :(</description></item></channel></rss>